<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Argus</title>
    <link>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Argus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 16:31:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How It Works</title>
      <link>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/docs/how-it-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 16:31:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/docs/how-it-works/</guid>
      <description>In this section we will dig into the lower level implementation of Argus to understand how it works, and provide those interested in contributing an introduction to the fundamentals of its design. An understanding of Go interfaces is recommended.
Running Argus In-Cluster Argus depends on communicating with the Kubernetes API Server. There are two ways to communicate with the API Server. In-cluster, and out-of-cluster. The kubectl CLI would be an example of out-of-cluster communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Device Tree Management</title>
      <link>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/docs/device-tree-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 17:55:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/docs/device-tree-management/</guid>
      <description>One of the main features of Argus is its ability to represent a Kubernetes cluster in LogicMonitor, and to keep that representation up to date and accurate. Argus achieves this by managing the following.
Device Groups Argus has an opinionated way of representing a cluster in the LogicMonitor Device Tree. It will first create a top level device group with the name of your cluster as specified in the arguments to the chart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/docs/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 17:54:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/docs/configuration/</guid>
      <description>Configuring the Collecorset Controller via the Helm Chart The Collectorset controller Helm chart supports the fololowing values:
Required Values:
 accessID: The LogicMonitor API key ID. accessKey: The LogicMonitor API key. account: The LogicMonitor account name. clusterName: A unique name given to the cluster&amp;rsquo;s device group.  Optional Values:
 enableRBAC (default: true): Enable RBAC. etcdDiscoveryToken: The public etcd discovery token used to add etcd hosts to the cluster device group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs</title>
      <link>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 16:29:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/docs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argus</title>
      <link>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/argus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 17:16:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/argus/</guid>
      <description>Warning
Argus is a community driven project in an alpha state. LogicMonitor support will not be able to assist with any issues related to Argus.
 Argus is a tool that helps users of LogicMonitor keep up with the highly dynamic topology of a Kubernetes cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 16:31:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/roadmap/</guid>
      <description> 0.1.x  Automated device group management Automated device management Automated device property management  0.2.x Automated collector management Support for all etcd discovery methods
0.3.x  Horizontal pod autoscaling based on LogicMonitor metrics.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 16:20:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>The simplest way to get started with Argus is to install it using Helm. Prior to installation, you will need a cluster-admin service account for tiller:
$ kubectl create serviceaccount tiller --namespace $NAMESPACE $ kubectl create clusterrolebinding tiller --clusterrole=cluster-admin --serviceaccount=$NAMESPACE:tiller $ helm init --service-account=tiller  You&amp;rsquo;ll also need to add the LogicMonitor chart repository:
$ helm repo add logicmonitor https://logicmonitor.github.com/k8s-helm-charts &amp;quot;logicmonitor&amp;quot; has been added to your repositories  Now you can install the LogicMonitor Collectorset controller:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/docs/monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 16:20:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://logicmonitor.github.io/k8s-argus/docs/monitoring/</guid>
      <description>Argus adds Kubernetes resources into LogicMonitor, but the DataSources that apply to those resources are responsible for monitoring. LogicMonitor has a set of developed modules for monitoring Kubernetes, which you can import via the LM Exchange (Settings | DataSources | Add | From LogicMonitor Exchange | Add by Locator Code) with these locator codes:
 Kubernetes_Nodes: PR4F33 Kubernetes_Node: 267H63 Kubernetes_Healthz: KZ463J Kubernetes_ControlPlane: N3GZNX Kubernetes_Service: HPJPRT Kubernetes_Scheduler: FCPJNH Kubernetes_Pod: P9TT2W Kubernetes_Container: 3AAJZX Kubernetes_PingK8s: 4N99FE  Once you&amp;rsquo;ve imported the DataSources, you should see monitoring for the health and performance of your Kubernetes Cluster in LogicMonitor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>